Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Brouillard Communications Vertical Files, 1931-2002 and undated RL.11021
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Brouillard Communications vertical files
1931-2002 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Brouillard Communications
John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
J. Walter Thompson Company
RL.11021
45 Linear Feet
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. Brouillard Communications, a division of JWT, was established in 1973 and specialized in business-to-business advertising and corporate communications. Brouillard closed in 2009. Collection consists of two alphabetical information and reference files for business category and individual company materials. Includes correspondence, research reports, clippings, tear sheets, printed corporate materials such as annual and quarterly reports, new business and client presentations. Companies represented include American Express, AT&T, Bethlehem Steel, Boeing, CIGNA, CIT, DuPont, General Electric, GTE (later Sprint), Honeywell, Hughes Aircraft (later Raytheon), IBM, International Paper, ITT, Kodak, Lockheed, McDonnell Douglas, Monsanto, Morgan Stanley, Motorola, Pennwalt, Pfizer, RJR Nabisco, Rockwell, Sharp, Shell, 3M, Travelers, TRW, Walt Disney, Westinghouse and Xerox. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Brouillard Communications Vertical Files were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2003
Arrangement
Organized into three series: Industries; Companies; and Audiovisual Materials.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
However, original audiovisual materials are closed to research until use copies can be produced.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48-hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Related Materials
Related materials may be found in the following JWT collections held in the Hartman Center:
Account Files Brouillard Communications Print Advertisements Corporation Vertical Files Information Center Vertical Files New Business Records
Collection Overview
Collection consists of two alphabetical information and reference files for business category and individual company materials. Includes correspondence, research reports, clippings, tear sheets, printed corporate materials such as annual and quarterly reports, new business and client presentations. Companies represented include American Express, AT&T, Bethlehem Steel, Boeing, CIGNA, CIT, DuPont, General Electric, GTE (later Sprint), Honeywell, Hughes Aircraft (later Raytheon), IBM, International Paper, ITT, Kodak, Lockheed, McDonnell Douglas, Monsanto, Morgan Stanley, Motorola, Pennwalt, Pfizer, RJR Nabisco, Rockwell, Sharp, Shell, 3M, Travelers, TRW, Walt Disney, Westinghouse and Xerox. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Clippings (information artifacts); Advertising -- United States -- History; Advertising -- United States -- 20th century; Advertising -- Research -- United States; Advertising -- Research; Advertising -- History; Advertising; Tear sheets; Monsanto Chemical Company; McDonnell Douglas Aerospace (Firm); Motorola, Inc; Morgan Stanley & Co; Pfizer Inc.; Pennwalt Corporation; RJR Nabisco (Firm); J. Walter Thompson Company. Brouillard Communications; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History; International Business Machines Corporation; J. Walter Thompson Company; International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation; International Paper Company; Lockheed Aircraft Corporation; Eastman Kodak Company; General Telephone & Electronics Corporation; General Electric Company; E.I. du Pont de Nemours & Company; CIGNA Worldwide (Firm); Boeing Aerospace Company; Bethlehem Steel Company; AT&T (Firm); American Express Company; Xerox Corporation; Westinghouse Electric Corporation; Walt Disney Company; TRW Automotive; Travelers Insurance Companies; 3M Company; Rockwell International; Honeywell Inc
- Industries, 1
  - Accounting, 1984-1991; (3 folders) (Box 1)
  - Aerospace, 1985-1990; (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Aircraft, 1989-1990 (Box 2)
  - Airlines, 1987-1994; (4 folders) (Box 2)
  - Banks, 1986-1991 (Box 2)
  - Banks, 1989-1996 (Box 3)
  - Banks--Mutual Funds, 1987-2003 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Beer, 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Brandy, 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Champagne and sparkling wine, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Coffee-flavored (Kahlua, Tia Maria, etc.), 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Courvoisier, 1989 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Fruit-flavored (Grand Marnier, etc.), 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Hennessey, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Irish (Bailey's, etc.), 1990-1991 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Italian (Sambuca, etc.), 1991-1992 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Long-running campaigns, 1988-1991 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Martell, 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Remy Martin, 1987-1989 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Scotch (Drambuie), 1989-1990 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Water, 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Beverages--Wine, 1989-1991 (Box 3)
  - Biotechnology, 1990 (Box 3)
  - Brokerage, 1984-1991 (Box 3)
  - Chemical, 1988-1991 (Box 3)
  - Computing--Computers, 1984-1991 (Box 4)
  - Computing--General, 1984-1994 (Box 4)
  - Computing--Hardware, 1989-1991 (Box 4)
  - Computing--Software, 1988-1991; (3 folders) (Box 4)
  - Consulting, 1988-1998 (Box 4)
  - Consumer electronics, 1989-1991 (Box 4)
  - Cosmetics--Almay, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Avon, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Aziza, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Borghese, 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Chanel, 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Charles of the Ritz, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Christian Dior, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Clarion, 1988-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Clinique, 1988-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Coty, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Cover Girl, 1988-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Elizabeth Arden, 1988-1990 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Estee Lauder, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Flame Glow, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Givenchy, 1990 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Guerlain, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Intelligent Skin Care, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Lancome, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--L'Oreal, 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Max Factor, 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Maybelline, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--No. 7, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Prescriptives, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Revlon, 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Rimmel, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Sally Hansen, 1988 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Shiseido, 1988-1990 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Ultima, 1988-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Visage Beaute, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Yves Saint Laurent, 1989-1991 (Box 5)
  - Cosmetics--Miscellaneous, 1989-1990 (Box 5)
  - Education, 1988-1994 (Box 5)
  - Electronic databases, 1986-1991 (Box 5)
  - Electronic mail, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Energy, 1984-1985 (Box 5)
  - Europe, 1987-1990 (Box 5)
  - Exchanges, 1990-1992 (Box 5)
  - Fashion, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
  - Fashion accessories--Handbags, 1989-1991 (Box 6)
  - Fashion accessories--Jewelry, 1986-1990 (Box 6)
  - Fashion accessories--Luggage, 1989-1991 (Box 6)
  - Fashion accessories--Miscellaneous, 1989-1991 (Box 6)
  - Fashion accessories--Shoes, 1989-1991 (Box 6)
  - Fashion accessories--Watches, 1989-1991; (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Financial, 1984-1992; (2 folders) (Box 6)
  - Food, 1987-1989 (Box 7)
  - Foreign, 1984-1987 (Box 7)
  - Forest products, 1987-1991; (2 folders) (Box 7)
  - Health care/HMO's, 1995-1998; (3 folders) (Box 7)
  - Health care/HMO's, 1995-1998; (3 folders) (Box 8)
  - Home furnishings--General, 1989-1991 (Box 8)
  - Home furnishings--China, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - Home furnishings--Crystal, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - Home furnishings--Furniture, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - Home furnishings--Kitchen, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
  - Home furnishings--Lighting, 1989-1991 (Box 8)
  - Home furnishings--Linens, 1989-1991 (Box 8)
  - Home furnishings--Silver, 1989-1991 (Box 8)
  - Home furnishings--Windows, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
  - Hospitals, 1989-1998 (Box 8)
  - Insurance, 1989-1992 (Box 8)
  - Insurance, 1984-1998; (7 folders) (Box 9)
  - Insurance, 1984-1999; (6 folders) (Box 10)
  - Insurance, 1990-1999; (5 folders) (Box 11)
  - Insurance, 1990-1992 (Box 12)
  - Insurance--Advertising, 1987-1994 (Box 12)
  - Insurance--Companies, 1990-1992 (Box 12)
  - Insurance--New business, 1990-1992; (2 folders) (Box 12)
  - International banks--General, 1991 (Box 12)
  - International banks--Deutsche Bank, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - International banks--NatWest, 1988-1990 (Box 12)
  - International banks--Standard Chartered, 1989 (Box 12)
  - International banks--Union Bank of Switzerland, 1986-1988 (Box 12)
  - Investment banks, 1984-1991 (Box 12)
  - Iron and steel, 1997 (Box 12)
  - Japan, 1989-1990 (Box 12)
  - Japan, 1990-1991 (Box 13)
  - Japan--Fujitsu, 1987-1991 (Box 13)
  - Japan--Hitachi, 1987-1990 (Box 13)
  - Japan--Toshiba, 1986-1990 (Box 13)
  - Korea, 1989-1991 (Box 13)
  - Legal firms, 1990-1997 (Box 13)
  - Liquor, 1989-1994; (4 folders) (Box 13)
  - Liquor, 1988-1992; (2 folders) (Box 14)
  - Liquor--Cordials, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Liquor--Gin, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Liquor--New Business, 1991-1992 (Box 14)
  - Liquor--Rum, 1989 (Box 14)
  - Liquor--Scotch and bourbon, 1990-1991 (Box 14)
  - Liquor--Vodka, 1989-1991 (Box 14)
  - Liquor--White liquors, 1990 (Box 14)
  - Local telephone, 1997 (Box 14)
  - Management consultants, 1997 (Box 14)
  - Media--General, 1989-1991 (Box 14)
  - Media--Cable, 1989-1991 (Box 14)
  - Media--Upscale magazines, 1989-1990 (Box 14)
  - Metals, 1988-1991 (Box 15)
  - Miscellaneous, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Mutual funds, 1990-1998; (6 folders) (Box 15)
  - Mutual funds, 1990-1998; (5 folders) (Box 16)
  - Mutual funds--Berger, 1986-1998 (Box 16)
  - Mutual funds--Janus, 1994-1996 (Box 16)
  - New Business--Office equipment, 1985-1990 (Box 16)
  - New Business--Office equipment, 1985-1990; (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Oil, 1984-1991; (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Paper, 1988-1995 (Box 17)
  - Pens, 1989-1991 (Box 17)
  - Pharmaceutical, 1984-1999; (2 folders) (Box 17)
  - Photography, 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Political, 1982 (Box 18)
  - Private banking, 1991-1997 (Box 18)
  - Professional services, 1991 (Box 18)
  - Publishers, 1977-1985 (Box 18)
  - Publishing, 1990 (Box 18)
  - Retail, 1984-1991; (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Retail clothiers, 1982-1991; (2 folders) (Box 18)
  - Schools, 1988-1990 (Box 18)
  - Skin care, 1989-1991 (Box 18)
  - Skin care, 1989-1991 (Box 19)
  - Space, 1990 (Box 19)
  - Specialty foods, 1988-1990 (Box 19)
  - Sporting goods, 1989-1991 (Box 19)
  - Sporting goods--Yachts, 1989-1990 (Box 19)
  - Statue of Liberty, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Stock exchanges, 1987-1991 (Box 19)
  - Telecommunications, 1984-1990; (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Telecommunications--AT&T, 1988 (Box 19)
  - Telecommunications--Electronic databases/mail services, 1984-1986 (Box 19)
  - Toiletries, 1988-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Aramis, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Beverly Hills, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Cacharel, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Calvin Klein Eternity, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Calvin Klein Obsession, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Carolina Herrera, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Chanel, 1988-1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Chloe, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Christian Dior, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Claiborne, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Clarins, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Clinique, 1987-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Elizabeth Arden, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Estee Lauder, 1988-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Fendi Roma, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Alfred Sung, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Estee Lauder Beautiful, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Elizabeth Taylor Passion, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Gloria Vanderbilt, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Givenchy, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Guerlain, 1986-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Lancome, 1989-1991 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Oscar de la Renta, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Paco Rabanne, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Paloma Picasso, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Prescriptives, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Ralph Lauren, 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Yves Saint Laurent, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Alberto Culver, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Calvin Klein, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Clairol, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Dep, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Helene Curtis, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--LCoupe, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--L'Oreal, 1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Neutrogena, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Pantene, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Paul Mitchell, 1989 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Revlon, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Studio, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Toiletries--Hair care--Vidal Sassoon, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Transportation, 1984-1990 (Box 20)
  - Travel, 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Travel--Cruise lines, 1989-1991 (Box 20)
  - Travel--Destinations, 1989-1990 (Box 20)
  - Travel--Hotels, 1990-1991 (Box 20)
  - Travel--Sabena, 1991 (Box 20)
  - Travel--SAS, 1991 (Box 20)
  - Trucking, 1985-1988 (Box 20)
  - Utilities/Telephone, 1989-1993 (Box 21)
- Companies, 2
  - AAAA (American Association of Advertising Agencies), 1990-1996 (Box 21)
  - ABC, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Acer, 1995 (Box 21)
  - ACL (Atlantic Container Line), 1983 (Box 21)
  - ADM (Archer Daniels Midland), 1981-1998 (Box 21)
  - ADR (Applied Data Research), 1984-1985 (Box 21)
  - ADT, 1988 (Box 21)
  - Advest, 1988 (Box 21)
  - AEG, 1987-1991 (Box 21)
  - Aerospatiale, 1990-1991 (Box 21)
  - Aetna, 1980-1998 (Box 21)
  - Agency advertisements, various, 1984-1990 (Box 21)
  - AHA (American Hospital Association), 1985 (Box 22)
  - AHF Marketing Research, 1986 (Box 22)
  - AICPA (American Institute of Certified Public Accountants), 1993-1999 (Box 22)
  - AIG, 1988-1998 (Box 22)
  - Airbus, 1985-1991 (Box 22)
  - Airco, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Air France, 1988 (Box 22)
  - Air Products and Chemicals, 1995 (Box 22)
  - AKZO, 1988-1991 (Box 22)
  - AlCan, 1984-1989 (Box 22)
  - Alcatel, 1987-1990 (Box 22)
  - Alcoa, 1931-1988 (Box 23)
  - Alfa-Laval, 1986-1990 (Box 23)
  - ALGA (American Loan Guarantee Association), 1987 (Box 23)
  - Allegheny International, 1983-1985 (Box 23)
  - Allegis, 1986-1987 (Box 23)
  - Allen-Bradley, 1984-1990 (Box 23)
  - Allendale Insurance, 1985-1990 (Box 23)
  - Alliance, 1985-1989 (Box 23)
  - Allianz, 1990 (Box 23)
  - Allied Signal, 1985-1997; (2 folders) (Box 23)
  - Allis-Chalmers, 1943-1980 (Box 23)
  - Allstate, 1990-1995 (Box 24)
  - Alltel, 1985-1990 (Box 24)
  - Aluminum Association, 1982-1991 (Box 24)
  - AMAX, 1981-1989 (Box 24)
  - Ambac Indemnity, 1990 (Box 24)
  - Amdahl, 1983-1994 (Box 24)
  - American Airlines, 1986-1988 (Box 24)
  - American Bookseller Association, 1990 (Box 24)
  - American Brands, 1987-1988 (Box 24)
  - American Can/Primerica, 1982-1987 (Box 24)
  - American Council of Life Insurance, 1987-1998 (Box 24)
  - American Cyanamid, 1947-1988; (2 folders) (Box 24)
  - American Electric Power, 1980-1998 (Box 25)
  - American Express, 1985-1992; (3 folders) (Box 25)
  - American Forest Council, 1988-1990 (Box 25)
  - American Gas Association, 1990 (Box 25)
  - American General, 1990-1998 (Box 25)
  - American Health Care Association, 1999 (Box 25)
  - American Home Products, 1988-1996 (Box 26)
  - American Medical Association, 1996-1997 (Box 26)
  - American Optical, 1947 (Box 26)
  - American Plastics Council, 1995-1996 (Box 26)
  - American Red Cross, 1990 (Box 26)
  - American Reinsurance (AmRe), 1990 (Box 26)
  - American Satellite, 1983-1984 (Box 26)
  - American Standard, 1995 (Box 26)
  - American Stock Exchange, 1995-1997 (Box 26)
  - Ameritech, 1984-1991 (Box 26)
  - AMF, 1976-1982 (Box 26)
  - Amoco, 1980-1991 (Box 26)
  - AMP, 1987-1990 (Box 26)
  - Ampex, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Amway, 1982-1991 (Box 26)
  - Anacomp, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Anderson Consulting, 1988-2000 (Box 26)
  - Anglo American Corporation of South Africa, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Anheuser-Busch, 1989-1991 (Box 27)
  - Apple, 1987-1989 (Box 27)
  - ARA, 1982-1984 (Box 27)
  - Aramco, 1981-1982 (Box 27)
  - Arco, 1974-1990 (Box 27)
  - Arianespace, 1990 (Box 27)
  - Arkwright, 1988 (Box 27)
  - Armco, 1947-1986 (Box 27)
  - Arthur Anderson, 1990-1998 (Box 27)
  - Arthur D. Little, 1995 (Box 27)
  - ASEA Brown Boveri, 1988-2000 (Box 27)
  - Association of American Railroads, 1938-1987 (Box 27)
  - Associations, various, 1982-1991 (Box 27)
  - Atlantic Mutual, 1985-1987 (Box 28)
  - Atlantic Richfield, 1973-1974 (Box 28)
  - AT&T, 1972-1990; (5 folders) (Box 28)
  - Austin, 1990 (Box 28)
  - AVCO, 1979-1983 (Box 28)
  - Aventis, 2000 (Box 28)
  - Avondale Mills, 1948 (Box 28)
    Scope and Contents note
    [Recruitment of African American graduates of Avondale community Negro school, quotes Booker T. Washington]
  - Babcock & Wilcox, 1977-1987 (Box 28)
  - Bally Mfg., 1986-1990 (Box 28)
  - Bank of America, 1988-1989 (Box 29)
  - Bankers Trust, 1986-1990 (Box 29)
  - Barclays Bank, 1985-1991 (Box 29)
  - BASF, 1986-1991 (Box 29)
  - BAT Industries, 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - Baxter, 1987-1994; (2 folders) (Box 29)
  - Bayer, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Bayer, 1987-1999 (Box 30)
  - Bayerische Landesbank, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Bean, L.L., 1990 (Box 30)
  - Bear Stearns, 1990-1995 (Box 30)
  - Beatrice Foods, 1984-1986 (Box 30)
  - Bechtel, 1971-1981 (Box 30)
  - Becker Paribas, 1984 (Box 30)
  - Beefeater's Gin, 1990 (Box 30)
  - Beer Institute, 1951-1952 (Box 30)
  - Bell & Howell, 1943-1990 (Box 30)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1984-1991 (Box 30)
  - Bell Atlantic, 1984-1991; (2 folders) (Box 31)
  - Bell Helicopter, 1984 (Box 31)
  - Bell Labs, 1965-1981 (Box 31)
  - Bell South, 1984-1990 (Box 31)
  - Bell Systems, 1982-1983 (Box 31)
  - Bendix, 1967-1983 (Box 31)
  - Benham-Holway Power Group, circa 1985 (Box 32)
  - BET Public Limited, 1988 (Box 32)
  - Bethlehem Steel, 1974-1988; (3 folders) (Box 32)
  - BHP (Australia), 1987 (Box 32)
  - Bif, 1991 (Box 32)
  - BIW (Bath Iron Works), 1983-1984 (Box 32)
  - Birmingham Steel, 1988 (Box 32)
  - Black & Decker, 1986 (Box 32)
  - Blenheim, Bruno, 1991 (Box 32)
  - Blount, 1990 (Box 32)
  - Blue Cross, 1985-1999 (Box 33)
  - Bodine, 1989 (Box 33)
  - Boeing, 1958-1997; (3 folders) (Box 33)
  - Boise Cascade, 1965-1992 (Box 33)
  - Bombardier, 1998 (Box 33)
  - Bonjour, 1989 (Box 33)
  - Borg Warner, 1947-1994; (2 folders) (Box 33)
  - Bosch, 1985-1991 (Box 33)
  - Boston Company, 1988 (Box 33)
  - BP America, 1989-1991 (Box 33)
  - British Aerospace, 1988-1991 (Box 33)
  - British Gas, 1990 (Box 33)
  - British Nuclear Fuels, 1990 (Box 33)
  - British Petroleum, 1988-1991 (Box 33)
  - British Steel, 1990-1991 (Box 33)
  - Brother Industries, 1990 (Box 34)
  - Browning Ferris, 1991-1998 (Box 34)
  - Brunswick, 1984-1988 (Box 34)
  - Bull (Honeywell), 1989-1991 (Box 34)
  - Bulova, 1991 (Box 34)
  - Bunker Ramo, 1979-1981 (Box 34)
  - Burlington Mills, 1973 (Box 34)
  - Burlington Northern Air Freight, 1983 (Box 34)
  - Burson-Marsteller, 1997 (Box 34)
  - Business One Irwin, 1990 (Box 34)
  - Business Week, 1988-1992 (Box 34)
  - Cable & Wireless, 1982-1996 (Box 34)
  - Cadbury Schwepps, 1990 (Box 34)
  - Campbell Soup, 1984-1987 (Box 34)
  - Canadian Imperial Bank of Commerce (CIBC), 1987 (Box 34)
  - Canon, 1989-1996 (Box 34)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, 1985-1991 (Box 34)
  - Carnation, 1985-1986 (Box 34)
  - Carrier, 1947-1984 (Box 34)
  - Cast, 1985-1991 (Box 34)
  - Catalyst Energy, 1987 (Box 34)
  - Caterpillar, 1986-1995 (Box 34)
  - CBI, undated (Box 34)
  - CD (Control Data), 1983-1985 (Box 34)
  - Celeron, 1981 (Box 34)
  - Cemex, 1997 (Box 34)
  - Centel, 1980-1990 (Box 34)
  - CF Company, 1985 (Box 34)
  - Champion International, 1979-1997; (2 folders) (Box 34)
  - Chase, 1987-1991; (2 folders) (Box 35)
  - Chemical Bank, 1987-1989 (Box 35)
  - Chemical Manufacturers Association, 1990-1995 (Box 35)
  - Chesebrough-Pond's, 1984-1986 (Box 35)
  - Chevron, 1988-1996 (Box 35)
  - Chicago Board of Trade, 1997 (Box 35)
  - Chicago Board Options Exchange, 1997 (Box 35)
  - Chrysler, 1943-1993 (Box 35)
  - Chubb, 1988-1991 (Box 35)
  - Ciba-Geigy, 1995-1998 (Box 35)
  - Cigna, 1982-1997; (3 folders) (Box 35)
  - CIT Group, 1986-1991; (3 folders) (Box 36)
  - Citibank, 1989-1990 (Box 36)
  - Citicorp, 1987-1999 (Box 36)
  - Cities Service (Citgo), 1979-1980 (Box 36)
  - Citizen, 1990 (Box 36)
  - CNA Financial, 1985-1997 (Box 36)
  - CNBC, 1991 (Box 36)
  - CNF Transportation, 1996-1997 (Box 36)
  - Coach, 1991 (Box 36)
  - Coca-Cola, 1975-1991 (Box 36)
  - Coleman, 1985-1986 (Box 36)
  - Collins & Aikman, 1978-1982 (Box 36)
  - Colt Industries, 1977-1984 (Box 36)
  - Combustion Engineering, 1983-1985 (Box 36)
  - COMEX, 1985 (Box 37)
  - Committee on Energy Awareness, 1982-1990 (Box 37)
  - Commodore, 1989 (Box 37)
  - Compaq, 1986-1995 (Box 37)
  - Computer Associates, 1994-1995 (Box 37)
  - Computerland, 1985-1989 (Box 37)
  - COMSAT, 1987-1989 (Box 37)
  - Conagra, 1985-1989 (Box 37)
  - Conner, 1989 (Box 37)
  - Conoco, 1974-1981 (Box 37)
  - Conrail, 1985-1988 (Box 37)
  - Conseco, 1997 (Box 37)
  - Consolidated Coal, 1987 (Box 37)
  - Container Corporation, 1970-1982 (Box 37)
  - Contel, 1984-1990 (Box 37)
  - Continental Airlines, 1987 (Box 37)
  - Continental Bank, 1986-1991 (Box 37)
  - Continental Grain, 1983-1985 (Box 37)
  - Continental Group, 1984 (Box 37)
  - Continental Insurance, 1982 (Box 37)
  - Cooper Industries, 1983-1990 (Box 37)
  - Coopers & Lybrand, 1989-1995 (Box 37)
  - Coors, 1985-1988 (Box 37)
  - Core Industries, 1985-1988 (Box 37)
  - CoreStates, 1984-1990 (Box 38)
  - Corning, 1988-1989 (Box 38)
  - Cosmopolitan, 1990 (Box 38)
  - Counter Intelligence, 1990 (Box 38)
  - CPT, 1981-1983 (Box 38)
  - Cray Research, 1995 (Box 38)
  - Credit Suisse, 1989-1998 (Box 38)
  - Crouse-Hinds, 1981 (Box 38)
  - Crownx, 1983 (Box 38)
  - CSX, 1983-1988; (2 folders) (Box 38)
  - Cullinet, 1983-1987 (Box 38)
  - Daewoo, 1984-1989 (Box 38)
  - Dai-Ichi Kangyo Bank, undated (Box 38)
  - Daimler-Benz, 1987-1991 (Box 38)
  - Dana, 1980-1997 (Box 38)
  - Data General, 1982-1991 (Box 38)
  - Data Point, 1985 (Box 38)
  - Day, 1987 (Box 38)
  - Dean Witter, 1989-1996 (Box 38)
  - DeBeers, 1990 (Box 38)
  - Deere (John), 1987 (Box 38)
  - Del Monte, 1991 (Box 38)
  - Deloitte & Touche, 1984-2000 (Box 38)
  - Delta Air Lines, 1989-1990 (Box 38)
  - Deutsche Aerospace, 1990 (Box 38)
  - Deutsche Bank, 1988-1990 (Box 38)
  - Deutsche Telekom, 1994-1996 (Box 38)
  - DG Bank, 1990 (Box 38)
  - DHL, 1985-1988 (Box 38)
  - Dial Group, 1995-1996 (Box 38)
  - Diamond International, 1967-1981 (Box 38)
  - Diamond Shamrock, 1976-1984; (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Diebold, 1991 (Box 39)
  - Digital Equipment Company (DEC), 1983-1991; (2 folders) (Box 39)
  - Dillingham, 1980 (Box 39)
  - DLJ, 1997 (Box 39)
  - Dornier, 1986 (Box 39)
  - Dow Chemical, 1947-1989 (Box 39)
  - Dow Corning, 1985 (Box 39)
  - Dow Jones, 1991 (Box 39)
  - Dresden Bank, 1991 (Box 39)
  - Dresser Industries, 1982-1998 (Box 39)
  - Drexel Burnham Lambert, 1986-1988 (Box 39)
  - Dreyfus, 1990-1999 (Box 39)
  - Duke Power, 1980s (Box 40)
  - Dun & Bradstreet, 1990-1991 (Box 40)